Guide to the Richard C. Levin Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Richard C. Levin papers
1963-1993
MS 1995
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
19.75
(42 boxes)
This collection comprises the papers of economist, professor, and former President of Yale University, Richard C. Levin. The papers document Levin's life and career prior to his presidency of Yale, including research that he performed, expert testimony based on his research, and resulting articles written for scholarly publications. Topics Levin focused on in these activities include deregulation, research and development, vertical integration in the oil industry, and transportation. The collection also contains teaching materials for courses Levin taught at Yale University and activities with professional organizations such as the American Economic Association, National Bureau of Economic Research and the National Science Foundation. Finally there is correspondence related to Levin's duties at Yale and his research. Materials date from 1963 to 1993.
Levin, Richard C., 1947-
Scope and Contents
This collection comprises the papers of economist, professor, and former President of Yale University, Richard C. Levin. The papers document Levin's life and career prior to his presidency of Yale, including research that he performed, expert testimony based on his research, and resulting articles written for scholarly publications. Topics Levin focused on in these activities include deregulation, research and development, vertical integration in the oil industry, and transportation. The collection also contains teaching materials for courses Levin taught at Yale University and activities with professional organizations such as the American Economic Association, National Bureau of Economic Research and the National Science Foundation. Finally there is correspondence related to Levin's duties at Yale and his research. Materials date from 1963 to 1993.
Biographical / Historical
Richard Charles Levin is an economist, professor of economics, and he served as the longest tenured president of Yale University from 1993 to 2013. His research interests include transportation economics, antitrust law and industrial competitiveness, intellectual propertty, and industrial research and development.
Levin was born in San Francisco, California on April 7, 1947. He graduated from Stanford University in 1968 with a Bachelor of Arts degree in history and subsequently received a Bachelor of Letters degree in politics and philosophy from Merton College, Oxford. Levin earned his PhD in economics from Yale University in 1974 and became an Assistant Professor of Economics at Yale that same year. He was promoted to Associate Professor in 1979, and in 1982 he was appointed Professor in Economics and Management at the Yale School of Management. Before being appointed president of Yale, Levin also served as chairman of the university's Economics Department and the Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences.
Levin's presidency of Yale was marked by many accomplishments, including significant growth of its endowment, higher undergraduate admission standards, significant infrastructure development and building renovations, and improved labor relations at the university. Following his retirement as President of Yale in 2013, Levin became the Chief Executive Officer of Coursera, a for-profit educational technology company.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged in five series: I. Correspondence, 1974-1990; II. Legal files, 1978-1993; III. Subject files, 1963-1993; IV. Teaching files, 1966-1992; V. Writings, 1976-1990.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Richard C. Levin, 2013.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the papers is restricted until January 1, 2034, or one year after the date of Richard C. Levin's death, whichever comes first, except to the extent that Yale Corporation Miscellaneous Bylaws Section 4 otherwise imposes access restrictions. Tenure evaluations of faculty at any institution and letters of recommendation for students and other persons are restricted for a period of 75 years from the date of the writing or 5 years after the death of the individual, whichever comes first.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
College presidents; Economics -- Research; Economics -- Study and teaching; Economists -- United States; Levin, Richard C., 1947-; Yale University -- Presidents; Yale University. Department of Economics; Yale University -- Faculty
- Correspondence, 1974-1990; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Series I comprises correspondence to and from Levin during his time as professor of economics at Yale University. Much of it concerns his research, requests for copies of papers written by Levin, invitations to appear at conferences to present his work, and requests for Levin to review manuscripts. There is also some correspondence between Levin and his students, as well as with Yale University officials.
  - 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1-7)
  - 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
- Legal files, 1978-1993; Series II
  Series II comprises documents from court cases in which Levin served as an expert witness. Topics include corporate mergers, rights of use in transportation such as trackage rights, and pricing of commodities.
  - Allen Myland Inc. vs. International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), deposition, 1986 December 29-30 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Chessie System Inc., verified statement and deposition, 1980 January (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chicago and Northwestern Transportation Company (CNW)
    - Statement and correspondence, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Verified statement concerning Wisconsin Central Transportation Company (WC), 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - City of Long Beach vs. Exxon Corporation
    - Outline, 1991 December 13 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Reporter's transcript of proceedings
      - Volumes 72-74, 1992 April 8-10 (Box 4, Folder 2-4)
      - Volumes 77-78, 1992 April 15-16 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Geisco, Inc. vs. Honeywell, Inc., transcript of Levin's testimony, 1981 June (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Graham Architectural Products Corporation, statement, Circa 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Laurel Sand and Gravel, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Kansas City Southern Railway (KCS)
    Arrangement
    Materials are arranged in chronological order.
    - Prior testimony/articles, 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Verified statements of witnesses on trackage rights, 1981 February 20 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Verified statement, draft, 1981 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Testimony on Union Pacific/Missouri Pacific, 1981 July 14 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Union Pacific/Missouri Pacific (UP/MP) testimony, 1981 July-October (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Verified statements of witnesses in rebuttal of Union Pacific/Missouri Pacific, 1981 October 5 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Verified statement on application for trackage rights, 1984 September 10 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Verified statements on Santa Fe Southern Pacific and errata, 1984 November 21 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Testimony, Circa 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
    - Verified statements on Union Pacific/Missouri Pacific, 1985 February 21 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Rebuttal statement of Dennis W. Carlton, 1985 May 15 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Verified statements in rebuttal - trackage rights, 1985 May 29 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Verified statements in rebuttal II- trackage rights, 1985 June 7 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Verified statements on Santa Fe Southern Pacific, 1986 February 27 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway (KCS) and Denver & Rio Grande Western Railroad proposals to acquire Southern Pacific Transportation Company, verified statement, 1987 March 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Verified statements, Union Pacific/Missouri Pacific, 1987 March 17 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Testimony since February 1987, 1987 March-1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Verified statements in opposition to trackage rights requests of Union Pacific/Missouri Pacific, 1987 June 15 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Rebuttal verified statements on trackage rights, 1987 July 13 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Verified statements on Southern Pacific, 1988 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Opposition verified statements on Rio Grande, 1988 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Rebuttal verified statements, volume 1, 1988 June 27 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Rio Grande Industries verified statement, 1990 June 4 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Ortho Pharmaceutical Corporation vs. Amgen, Inc.
    - Defendant's Exhibit Number 968, "Report on Amgen's Damage Claims," prepared by Richard C. Levin, 1991 November 25 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Deposition exhibits, 1991 September 13-14 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Endispute arbitration deposition, volumes 1-3, 1991 September 13-November 22 (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
    - Levin estimates, 1991 October (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Plaintiff's Exhibits Numbers 392 and 393, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
    - Report on Amgen's damage claims, prepared by Richard C. Levin, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  - Petroleum products antitrust litigation
    - Deposition of Richard C. Levin
      - Volumes 1A-4, 1990 October 4-10 (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
      - Volume 5A-8, 1991 October 11-1992 August 15 (Box 11, Folder 1-6)
    - Exhibits to the Deposition of Richard C. Levin
      - 314-001 through 314-007, volumes 1-2, 1990 October 4-5 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
      - 314-037 through 314-044, volume 7, 1991 August 14 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - 314-045 through 314-056, volume 8, 1991 August 15 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Pinney Dock, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Trans-Alaska Pipeline System
    Material listed chronologically.
    - Confidential exhibits to the prepared direct testimony, 1983 November 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Exhibits to the prepared direct testimony, 1983 November 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Prepared direct testimony, 1983 November 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Prepared rebuttal testimony, 1983 December 23 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Testimony, 1984 January 23 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Workpapers to prepared testimony and rebuttals, Circa 1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Subject files, 1963-1993; Series III
  Series III comprises a mixture of materials related to Levin's academic career and interests. Much of it consists of notes, articles and reports pertaining to his research interests. The series also includes materials related to professional obligations, including documents from organizations and workshops in which he participated, and articles he refereed for publication.
  - General
    - 1983-1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Articles refereed, 1974-1988 (Box 14, Folder 3-9)
  - Biotechnology, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Carter memorandum, 1976, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Clinton, Bill, 1989-1992, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Computing, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Conferences
    - Dartmouth, 1974 August 25-29 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Lehigh, May 25, 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER)
      - Industrial Organization (IO), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
      - Technical Change, August 10-12, 1983 August-September (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Trade Policy, September 17-18, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), Intellectual Property Rights (IPR), May 8-9, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
    - Paris, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Parker, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Regulation and Innovation, 1979 May 8-9 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Resources and Economic History, Bellagio, Italy, 1977 April 12-18 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - School of Organization and Management (SOM), 1980 November (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), 1974 August 12-16 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Data
    - Beggs patent, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Brown: New York Telephone, 1969-1986 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Company, 1983, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Establishment, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Import, Undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Input-output 4-digit
      - 1963, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - 1967, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Line of business (LB), 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Line of business (LB), Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Major League Baseball salary arbitration, 1986-1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1980 summer (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Notes on data collection and use, 1968-1980, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Oil - vertical integration, 1976-1987, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - OTAF patent, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Research and development (R&D), 1969-1986 (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
    - Research and development (R&D) concentration data - contacts and sources, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Scherer research and development (R&D) and Federal Trade Commission (FTC) data, Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Yale interindustry data base, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Density tapes - edit, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Departmental committees, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Depreciation regressions, 1977 July (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Econometrics - pooling, 1966-1971, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Economic references, 1973-1980, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Economics of Organization, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Firm size and research & development intensity, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Grants and opportunities
    - General, 1980-1987 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
    - Eno Foundation, 1977-1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Foundations - research support, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Kent Healy Fund, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER) proposal, 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) grant
      Material is arranged chronologically.
      - Phase I, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Program - key documents, 1978-1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Proposal, 1980 March (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Collected papers, 1982, undated (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
      - Year One Report, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - "Dynamic Competition: A Program of Research on Technological Change and Market Structure" progress reports, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Year 2 collected papers, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
      - Year 2 progress report, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Supplemental funding, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Grant documents, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Science and Technology Centers proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Proposal review, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Sloan Foundation, 1974-1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Handouts, miscellaneous -- appropriability, 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - HBS, February 29, 1985, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - House Judiciary Committee, 1974-1976, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Introduction to Ricardian economics, 1973, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Investment theory, 1966-1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Journal of Industrial Economics (JIE), 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Laurel Sand and Gravel (LSG), 1991 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Logit - probit, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Marxian economics, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Meetings
    - American Economic Association (AEA)
      - 1980 September-December (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - 1987 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Cartels session, Monday, December 28, 10:15 a.m., 1987 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Productivity session, 1980 December (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Research and development (R&D) session, December 29, 8:00 a.m., 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Research and development (R&D) funding and giving session, December 28, 8:00 a.m., 1987 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - American Economic Association (AEA)/American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) research and development (R&D) spillovers session, December 28, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Boston University Law Symposium, October 19, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Cooperative Research (CCR) - Association of Yale Alumni (AYA) Assembly, 1985 October (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER) Productivity Group, March 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Public Choice Society panel on government administration of markets and resources, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Transportation Research Board (TRB) annual meeting, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Yale Law and Policy Symposium, September 27, 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Yale University Research Program on Technological Change response for June 8, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Mondale, Walter, 1982 April (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF)
    - Advisory Panel, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Proposal evaluation - Griliches, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Venture memorandum, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Yale Club meeting followup correspondence, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - New York League Consortium, 1989 October 3 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Parker, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Photocopiers, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Presentations, 1974-1981 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Railroads and transportation
    - Abandonments, Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Baumol rail rate statement, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Census of Transportation, 1972, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Conrail, 1978-1979, undated (Box 25, Folder 3-5)
    - DeHayes time data; timecost regressions and fits, 1975, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Department of Transportation (DOT)
      - Replies to Senate Subcommittee on Surface Transportation regarding 4R Act, 1979 March (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - "Report on the Regulatory Reform Provisions of the 4R Act", 1979 July (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Effects of truck deregulation, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company (GTW) case, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC) accounting rules, 1977, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Merger guidelines, 1968, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Piggyback data and Xeroxed articles, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Rail cost computations, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Rail investment data, 1975-1977, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Rail mergers study, 1986 March (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Rail, truck cost data and computations, 1975, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Rail, truck cost tables, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Railroad data tapes, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Railroad investment, model, 1977, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Railroad investments, articles and data, 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Railroad lecture, 1975 November (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Railroad mergers, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Railroad notes, 1979-1983, undated (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
    - Railroad rates of return, 1979, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Railroad rate of return calculations, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Railroads - international comparisons, Undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Railroads: references, data sources, Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Unit trains, 1963, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - United States Department of Transportation restricted release aviation economic information policy, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Research and development (R&D) survey
    - General, 1981-1982, undated (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - Executive summary, 1984, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Mailing to respondents, 1984 May (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Paper draft, 1984 July (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Questionnaire on Industrial Research and Development
      - R&D business, returned forms 001-, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Response from General Foods, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Responses, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Research Policy
    - Articles refereed, 1981-1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Editorial correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Reviews requested, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Reviews
    - Book reviews, 1974-1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Braun-Macdonald review, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Journal of Economic History review article, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Mansfield texts reviewed, 1978-1981 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Robotics/semiconductors, 1983, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Schumpeter Society, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Schumpeterian Competition
    - General, 1978-1981, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Bell Journal of Economics (BJE), 1981 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Comments and correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Master, short version, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Papers, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - School of Management (SOM) Number 43, Series A, 1981 July (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Semiconductor clippings, 1980-1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Seminars
    - Berkeley, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Economics seminars and activities, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Instoria - Providentia, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1987 February (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Methodology, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER), summer, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF)
      - 1983 February 24 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Productivity Improvement Research (PIR), January 7, 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Rail deregulation seminar material, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Regulation, Implementation, and Health Policy Seminar, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Seminars on Schumpeterian Competition, 1979 Apr, November (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - University of Connecticut (UConn), 1978 April 24 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Senate Judiciary Committee, 1987 May 7 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Speaking engagements, 1975-1992 (Box 31, Folder 5-11)
  - Stamford Schools, 1983 April 28 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - State economic development programs, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Swarthmore examinations, 1978-1983 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - "Telecommunications Services as a Strategic Industry: Implications for a U.S. Public Policy," by Robert G. Harris, 1990 June 15 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - University Microfilms, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Van Buren, Eleanor, retirement, 1986 June 26 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Vertical integration, correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Workshops
    - Chicago workshop handout, 1985 March (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Economics of Television, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Industrial Research and Development Survey
      - June 8 meeting planning and notes, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Packet and notes, 1984 June 8 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER)
      - Trade, 1984 April (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Trade Policy, August 9, 1983 June-August (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF)
      - Intellectual Property and Trade, 1985 November 21 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Predatory Research and Development (R&D), June 9, 1983 May-June (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Telecommunications, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Transfer of Technology, Economic Growth Center (ECG), 1974 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Yale University Research Program on Technical Change Policy Discussion Paper Series, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Teaching files, 1966-1992; Series IV
  Series IV comprises materials related to classes that Levin taught at Yale University. Materials include lecture notes, course outlines, reading lists, and examinations.
  - Economics 30/150, lecture notes, 1976-1977, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Economics 95 - 2b
    - Course outline and reading list, Undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Lecture notes, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Economics 110
    - Examinations, 1974-1990 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Reading lists and problem sets, 1974-1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)